Amanda Steele Show. It's time for us to get into the Big Up Let Down. Today's goes to
an almost bride-to-be in California for her generosity and foresight. So this anonymous
woman in Cali, she learned some incendiary information about her fiance and decided to
call the wedding off. However, she had already paid a $15,000 non-refundable fee for the wedding
reception. She donated the reception party to a non-profit which provides community support to
parents with children who have special needs. And some people would have said, baby, we have in this
reception whether you get married or not. And today's goes to piss poor journalism and cultural
appropriation during Black History Month. Super Bowl bound Chiefs player Travis Kelsey made the news
recently. No, no, no, not for his girlfriend. But for popularizing the fade haircut with disrespect.
There's even a TikTok video from barber Nigel Miller who said that his client was going for the
quote-unquote Kelsey look. You're going for the Black man fade. That's the look that Kelsey was
going for. And he probably started getting that fade when he was dating the sister. There's so many
fades. There's a temple fade. There's a high top fade. There's a boozy fade. You know, there's many
fades, but none of them are Kelsey fades. Not a single one.
We are, we are, we are.